ekstop.com 2015-03-14

# 

Thank you for visiting EkStop.com's privacy policy. We provide the best standards in our customer's information privacy and in relation to their secure transactions on [EkStop.com](http://www.ekstop.com/). Please review our privacy policy periodically for updates and feel free to contact us at [legal@EkStop.com](mailto:legal@EkStop.com) if you have any questions. 

Collection of Information

When you setup an account with us, contact us, or participate in activities on our site, we gather personal information from you such as name, e-mail address, mobile phone number, etc. When you visit our site, we may maintain some information about your visit such as your computer's IP, browser type, time visited, etc. 

Use of Information

We use personal information to personalize and customize the product and service to you. In addition, we use the information to promote services to you and for product improvement purposes. We also use the information troubleshoot issues; for our safety and to protect us against error, fraud, and crimes; diagnose problems; as advised as time of information collection; and to administer the terms and conditions. We may share this information with other corporate affiliates and entities for the same reasons mentioned above. 

Links to other sites

You may come across links to other sites as you browse our site. EkStop.com's privacy policies to not apply in those other sites. We cannot be in charge for the reliability of the service and data of the other sites, and thus are not responsible for their privacy policy. We recommend you to read the other sites's privacy policy. 

Cookies

Cookies are small identifiers that is sent from a web server to web browser and then stored on your computer's hard drive to identify you and to understand how you arrived at our website. We use both temporary and permanent cookies to maintain your security and improve your experience with our product. Access to EkStop.com requires that cookies are enabled on your browser settings. 

Opt-out

Please contact EkStop.com at [cs@EkStop.com](mailto:cs@EkStop.com), if you no longer wish to receive non-essential and marketing material from you. 

Security Safeguards

EkStop.com uses stringent security guidelines and some of the highest security standards to protect our customers from security issues, and any loss and misuse of their information. 

Questions

Feel free to contact EkStop.com at [ legal@EkStop.com](mailto:legal@EkStop.com) for any further questions on our privacy policy.
